https://store.flagshiptech.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Statement
Flagship Technologies is aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously and demonstrate a strong commitment to online privacy. In acknowledgment of that commitment, we have adopted a comprehensive policy to safeguard the privacy of all visitors to the Flagship Technologies website.
Collection of Data
Flagship Technologies store data on our servers for various security reasons. This data may include the name of your Internet service provider, click sources, the websites that you visit from our site, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. This information can be used to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, to help identify you, and to gather broad demographic information.
The data we collect will only be used for the purpose of supplying you with the requested products or services, company marketing purposes, or for other reasons for which you have given your consent, except where otherwise provided by law.
Security
Flagship Technologies uses technical and organizational security precautions to protect your data from manipulation, loss, destruction or access by unauthorized persons.
We do not collect, process, or use on our website, any information relating to an individual whom we know to be under 13 years old, without the prior, verifiable consent of his or her legal representative. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.
Disclaimer
This site contains links to other sites. Flagship Technologies is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.
Contact Us
Please contact Flagship Technologies technical experts if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy.
